Guide to the Joe Negri Collection, 1930-2014 CAM.JNC.2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Joe Negri Collection
1930-2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Negri, Joe
CAM.JNC.2014
16 Linear Feet
The Joe Negri Collection contains the original scores, notes, and sound recordings documenting Joe Negri's career from his earliest days performing with his brother, through his years at then Carnegie Tech, up to his current work as a jazz guitarist.
Scope and Content Notes
The Joe Negri Collection consists of scores of Joe Negri's radio and TV jingles; scores written during his time at Carnegie Tech up to present day including "Beat 'em Bucs" the Pittsburgh Pirates fight song and works composed for "Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood;" both published and unpublished sound recordings of Mr. Negri and others performing his songs; scripts and lyrics from the Beck's Charter Oaks shows performed with Don Brockett; published songbooks from a variety of composers; film scores Mr. Negri composed for WQED, WTAE and various private firms; and assorted programs and proposals for American music concerts.
Biography
From joenegri.com:
In 1999, the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust honored me by naming me the "Established Artist of the Year." I remember telling them that my career has been a "work in progress" since age three.
As a child performer, I performed on radio and appeared in theatrical and stage productions throughout the tri-state area. I was even chosen to become one of Pittsburgh's "Stars of Tomorrow." A voice change shattered my confidence and I stopped performing. Shortly after, I began to seriously study the guitar.
By age sixteen, I was playing well enough to win a job with one of the country's top swing bands. I soon became a featured member of the band and traveled nationally with them for about two years. Though the army briefly sidetracked my career, it by no means stopped it. I was fortunate enough to meet up with several top-notch jazz musicians and together we continued to develop our musical skills.
In the early 50's, I enrolled at CMU (Carnegie Tech) and I picked up some important musical training and overall grooming. I feel very strongly that these years rounded me as a person and prepared me for the work that was still to come. Following CMU, I landed a job in the "brand new" media of television. It was the start of a forty-year career. My TV work began at KDKA-TV where I headed up my own trio and following that, I spent some twenty years at WTAE-TV (Pittsburgh's ABC affiliate) as an "on the air performer" and musical director.
Love and Marriage
It was during this time that I met, feel in love with, and married Joni Serafini. Shortly after that, Joni and I began to seriously consider moving to NYC even though my career was beginning to take shape here in Pittsburgh. New York City has always been the mecca for artist and music was no exception. The recording studios, the major radio stations, and major TV networks represented the "Holy Grail" of the music business in the middle of the last century. Our first daughter, Lisa, was born a few years after we were married. A year or so later, we decided that we should look into opportunities in the Big Apple!
We visited with several musician friends and we surveyed the music scene closely. Even though the opportunities seemed abundant, we chose to return to Pittsburgh. The thought of raising Lisa and a family in that environment discouraged any ideas of becoming a New York studio musician.
Life has a strange way of working things out. It came to pass that the studios were to undergo a revolutionary transformation. The 60's brought great changes to the recording industry and the TV studios. We have never regretted our decision to return to Pittsburgh.
Joe - The Guitarist
My current professional bio states that I'm one of the most recognized names in Pittsburgh music circles and perhaps one of the best jazz guitarists in the country. I started playing the guitar when I was eight years old.
As one wit remarked, "Joe Negri was playing the guitar long before it was fashionable." My life, in many ways, parallels the history of the jazz guitar. I grew up listening to and emulating guitarists like Charlie Christian, Les Paul, and Django Reinhart. I consider myself to be a part of the second wave of jazz guitarists that came into prominence after World War II. Some of my peers included Johnny Smith, Jimmy Raney, Wes Montgomery, Tal Farlow, Herb Ellis, Barney Kessel, Joe Pass, and Kenny Burrell.
I'm known to millions of children for my appearances as "Handyman Negri" on the PBS show "Mister Rogers Neighborhood." That is a role I have played for over 30 years. As a composer, I have written music for many documentary film scores. In addition, my credits include The Crossing (scored for Brass Band and Jazz Trio).
I have just finished writing my first guitar method book. It is an introduction to improvisation entitled: "A Common Sense Approach to Guitar Improvisation." The book will be published by Mel Bay Publications and should be ready for release early in 2001.
And so, the "work in progress" moves on into the 21st century. I pray that the music continues and that I continue to write, teach, and perform as long as I am able to do so with style and grace...
Acquisition Information
Joe Negri donated his collection of original scores, songbooks, memorabilia and recordings to the Center for American Music at the University of Pittsburgh in 1999. In the fall of 1999, the director of the Center, Dr. Deane Root, interviewed Mr. Negri about the collection to further clarify the contents. A transcript of this interview, as well as the original recording, have been added to the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Original Compositions
Series II. Published Sheet Music
Series III. Songbooks
Series IV. Recordings
Series V. Compositions by Robert McCully
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Sound recordings; Sheet music; Scores; Musicians -- United States; Music -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; WQED (Television station: Pittsburgh, Pa.).; WTAE-TV (Television station: Pittsburgh, Pa.); Brockett, Don; McCully, Robert J.; Negri, Joe
- Original Compositions, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Original compositions written by Joe Negri divided into the following categories: Radio & TV Jingles; Compositions co-written with Robert J. McCully; Compositions written for the Beck's Charter Oaks Shows; Compositions written for films; Early Compositions and those created for College; Compositions written for the River City Brass Brand; Compositions written for the Poetry Forums; and Commissioned Compositions.
  - Radio and TV Jingles, 1.
    - "What'cha Smilin' About" [Eat 'n Park] (Box 3, Folder 151-153)
    - Landmark Savings Jingle (version 1) (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1534.01)
      Typed lyrics.
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Radio-T.V. spots Originals
    - Landmark Savings Jingle (version 2) (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1534.02)
      typed lyrics.
    - "People to People" melody (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1534.1)
      holograph score for landmark savings jingle "People to People." on verso is a letter dated August 28, 1984, to Joe Negri from John K. Lally discussing the project.
    - "Today's Home" master lead (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1535)
      Holograph manuscript of master lead.
    - "Today's Home" electric bass (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1535.1)
      holograph manuscript.
    - Monroeville Mall (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1536)
      Holograph manuscript.
    - "Harlequin" (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1537)
      Holograph manuscript. 4 pages. Original and two photocopies.
    - "There's a Tavern in the Town" (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1539)
      holograph manuscript. 4 pages.
    - "Tavern in Town" accomp. piano (Box 16, Folder 1534-1539, Item 1539.1)
    - "Happy Days" (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1540)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 pages.
    - "Poison Song" (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1541)
    - West Penn AAA (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1542)
    - West Penn Triple A Flute (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1542.1)
    - West Penn Triple A Voice (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1542.2)
    - Kaufman's, February 9, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1543)
      Holograph manuscript. original and 1 copy.
    - Alcoa Spots R450 (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1545)
    - Alcoa Spots bass (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1545.1)
    - Alcoa Spots trumpet (Box 16, Folder 1540-1545, Item 1545.2)
    - Aluminum Company of America "The Way a New Car Looks" (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1599)
      Typed script for 1 minute commercial. Two copies.
      Contents originally enclosed in manila envelope with the following inscription:
      Alcoa-spots Music Punctuation
    - Aluminum Company of America "Jet Plane" (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1600)
      Typed script for commercial. Two copies.
    - Aluminum Company of America "It's a Fact..." (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1601)
      Typed script for commercial.
    - Aluminum Company of America "Cool, air-conditioned driving" (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1602)
    - Aluminum Company of America "You Can't Beat Aluminum" (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1603)
    - Aluminum Company of America "My husband says" (Box 17, Folder 1599-1604, Item 1603A)
    - Alcoa-Co (Box 17, Folder 1649-1651, Item 1650)
    - Alcoa Corporate guitar (Box 17, Folder 1649-1651, Item 1650.1)
      holograph manuscript. 1 page.
    - Alcoa - corporate bass (Box 17, Folder 1649-1651, Item 1650.2)
    - Kilowatt - OHM - Electricity (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1653)
      Holograph manuscript. 4 pages.
    - Kilowatt - Ohm - Electricity (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1653.1)
      Holograph manuscript. 3 pages.
    - Kilowatt - OHM - Elec. (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1653.2)
      holograph manuscript. 3 pages. Two copies.
    - Leadership (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1654)
      Holograph manuscript. 1 page. 3 copies.
    - Leadership bass (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1654.1)
    - Leadership drums (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1654.2)
      Holograph manuscript. 1 page.
    - Leadership No. 4 (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1654.3)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 pages. voice and piano.
    - Leadership (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1654.4)
      holograph manuscript. 2 pages.
    - "Appointments" (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1655)
      Holograph manuscript. 10 pages.
    - Appointments (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1655.1)
      holograph manuscripts. 5 pages.
    - Opening bass (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1655.2)
    - Opening drums (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1655.3)
      holograph score. 1 page.
    - Saleman's Song (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1656)
    - Salesman (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1656.1)
    - Lets [sic] Get this Load on the Road voice (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1656A)
    - Lets [sic] Get This Load on the Road (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1656A.1)
    - Lets [sic] Get this Load on the Road (Box 17, Folder 1653-1656, Item 1656A.2)
    - Aluminum Company of America "Brakes" (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1657)
      Sixty second commercial script. 1 page.
      Contents originally enclosed in brown envelope with the following inscription:
      ALCOA - Radio Spots July 21, 1965
    - Brakes (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1657.1)
    - Brakes bass (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1657.2)
    - Brakes drums (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1657.3)
    - Aluminum company of America Trim, May 11, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1658)
      Typed script. 2 pages. On verso of 2nd page is a handwritten song called "Waltz for Debbie."
    - Trim bass (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1658.1)
    - Trim guitar (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1658.2)
    - Air conditioning/Trim flute (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1658.3)
    - Air Conditioning drums (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1658.4)
    - Air conditioning bassoon (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1659.1)
    - Air Conditioning piano (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1659.2)
    - Air conditioning flute (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1659.3)
    - ALCOA Spot (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1660)
    - Untitled (Box 17, Folder 1657-1660, Item 1661)
      Holograph manuscript. half page.
    - Sun Drug (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1554)
      Sun Drug Spot and Eiben and Irr
      Joe Negri R.J. MCully for Lou Sautel Agn. August 1978
    - "Sun Drug Jingle" (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1555)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notes.
    - Sun Drug :60 second (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.01)
    - Sun Drug :30 second (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.02)
    - Sun Drug: 60 second vocal (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.11)
    - Sun Drug 30 sec. vocal (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.12)
    - Sun Drug 60 second guitar (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.2)
    - Sun Drug Spot :60 second bass (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.3)
      holograph manuscript. 30 second version on verso. Contents originally enclosed in manila envelope with the following inscription:
    - Sun Drug :60 second drums (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1556.4)
    - "Eiben and Irr", August 11, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1557)
    - "Eiben and Irr" piano (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1558)
    - "Eiben and Irr" vocal (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1558.1)
    - "Eiben and Irr" guitar (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1558.2)
    - "Eiben and Irr" Bass (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1558.3)
    - "Eiben and Irr" Drums (Box 16, Folder 1554-1558, Item 1558.4)
    - Westinghouse Recruiting vocal (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1585)
    - Westinghouse trumpet (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1585.1)
    - Westinghouse bass (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1585.2)
    - Westinghouse Blues (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1585.3)
    - Thrift Drug (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1586)
      Holograph Manuscript. 2 pages.
    - Thrift Drug (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1586.1)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten changes.
    - Thrift Drug :20 (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1586.2)
    - Waterford Park vocals (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1586A)
      Holograph manuscript with :30 and :10 versions of vocal.
    - Waterford Park bass & drums (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1586A.1)
    - Unconventional 4 guitar (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1587)
    - Unconventional 4 bass (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1587.1)
    - Unconventional 4 vocal (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1587.2)
    - Unconventional 4 drums (Box 16, Folder 1585-1587, Item 1587.3)
    - Laurel Mountains (Box 17, Folder 1591-1594, Item 1591)
    - Horne's Warehouse (Box 17, Folder 1591-1594, Item 1592)
    - Horne's Warehouse Clearance (Box 17, Folder 1591-1594, Item 1592.1)
      Typed script and lyrics for Horne's commercial. 1 page.
    - U.S. Steel guitar (Box 17, Folder 1595-1598, Item 1597)
    - U.S. Steel clarinet (Box 17, Folder 1595-1598, Item 1598)
    - Austin's (is a grand old name) (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613)
    - Austin's piano/keyboard (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.1)
    - Austin's vocal (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.2)
    - Austin's (grand old name) guitar (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.3)
    - Austin (grand old name) electric bass (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.4)
    - Austin's drums (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.5)
    - Austin's 30-second Television Commercial (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1613.6)
      Typed script for commercial. 1 page.
    - Wheeling Downs (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1614)
    - Wheeling Downs 60 second jingle (Box 17, Folder 1605-1614, Item 1614.1)
      Typed lyrics. 1 page.
    - Concord Savings and Loan (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1632)
      holograph manuscript. Also contains pieces entitled "Rainbow of Color" and "Bossa Nova." 3 pages.
    - "Advertising Week in Pittsburgh" (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1633)
    - Duquesne Light Company (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1634)
    - Gimbles (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1635)
    - Thorofare (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1636)
    - Thorofare (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1636.1)
    - Thorofare (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1636.2)
    - Thorofare Markets, March 26, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1637)
      Recording script. Typed. Two pages, two copies.
    - "Washington, PA" (Box 17, Folder 1632-1640, Item 1640)
    - Vimco Jingle (Box 17, Folder 1645-1648, Item 1645)
      handwritten lyrics. 1 page.
    - Vimco (Box 17, Folder 1645-1648, Item 1646)
      Vimco lyrics. 1 page. Handwritten.
    - McDonald's (Box 17, Folder 1645-1648, Item 1647)
      Handwritten lyrics on KDKA 2 TV stationary. 1 page.
    - McDonald's Radio (Box 17, Folder 1645-1648, Item 1648)
      Handwritten notes on McDonald's radio spot. 1 page.
    - May Gro Spot (Box 17, Folder 1645-1648, Item 1651)
    - Westland Milk Jingle (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1666)
      Contents originally enclosed in a manila envelope with the following inscription:
      Music to: Westland Milk Spots Jan - 1967 Joe Negri Bob McCully Geo. Hill Agency
    - Westland Milk vocal (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1667)
    - Westland Milk vocal (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1667.1)
    - Westland Milk flute (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1667.2)
    - Westland Milk bass (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1667.3)
    - Westland Milk vibes (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1667.4)
    - Westland (Inst) guitar (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1668.1)
    - Westland (instrum) flute (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1668.2)
    - Westland (Inst) bass (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1668.3)
      Holograph manuscript. 1 page. Contents originally enclosed in a manila envelope with the following inscription:
    - Westland (Instrumental) vibes (Box 18, Folder 1666-1670, Item 1668.4)
  - Compositions with Bob McCully, 2.
    - "Wonder If" (Box 2, Folder 100-111, Item 108)
      Printed score with guitar chords. Two copies.
    - "Wonder If" manuscript (Box 2, Folder 125-130, Item 125)
    - "Wonder if" manuscript (Box 2, Folder 125-130, Item 125.1)
    - "Wonder If" manuscript (Box 2, Folder 125-130, Item 125.2)
      manuscript and photocopy.
    - "When Love Comes Calling" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 168)
      Holograph manuscript. Music by Joe Negri, lyrics by Bob McCully Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "Victim of Love" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 169)
    - "Wait for Me" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 170)
    - "Crazy Crew Cut sort of Guy" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 171)
    - "Lisa" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 172)
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 3, Folder 168-173, Item 173)
    - "I Found My Love" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 174)
    - "Tormented" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 175)
    - "Airline Stewardess" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 176)
    - "Wait for Me" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 177)
    - "Charge of the Bucanneers" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 178)
      Holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "Porto Bay" (Box 3, Folder 174-179, Item 179)
    - "I Found My Love" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 180)
    - "Victim of Love" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 181)
    - "I Found My Love" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 182)
    - "Tormented" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 183)
      guitar only. Holograph manuscript. Music by Joe Negri, lyrics by Bob McCully Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "When You Are Lonely" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 184)
    - "The Old Casino" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 185)
    - "Charlie" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 186)
      Photostat of Holograph manuscript. Music by Joe Negri, lyrics by Bob McCully Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "Crazy Crew Cut Sort of Guy" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 187)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript. Music by Joe Negri, lyrics by Bob McCully Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "Tormented" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 188)
    - "Where Did the Time Go?" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 189)
      Typed lyrics only. Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "I Like the Girls" (Box 3, Folder 180-185, Item 190)
    - "Misty Valley" (Box 3, Folder 191-193, Item 191)
    - "When Love Comes Calling" (Box 3, Folder 191-193, Item 192)
      Photostat of h olograph manuscript. Music by Joe Negri, lyrics by Bob McCully Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: Original Lead Sheets Songs: Joe Negri/Bob McCully from Beck's Shows
    - "Wait for Me" (Box 3, Folder 191-193, Item 193)
    - [Untitled to the tune of "Old Man River"] (Box 3, Folder 194-199, Item 194)
      typed lyrics to untitled piece with handwritten corrections
    - [Untitled; first line, "this is the story of Charlie Banana" (Box 3, Folder 194-199, Item 195)
      typed Lyrics (?) on onion skin paper. 5 pages.
    - "Bruce" (Box 3, Folder 194-199, Item 196)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notations (3 pages).
    - "An Evening Without Zsa Zsa Gabor", 1962 (Box 4, Folder 235)
      Complete typed script with handwritten notations authored by Joe Negri and Bob McCully. Bound. Pages unnumbered.
    - "Desdamona Fink Bass Book Act 1" (Box 4, Folder 236-237, Images 236)
      wire bound manuscript book with handwritten scores.
    - "Act II An Evening Without Desdamona Fink" Bass (Box 4, Folder 236-237, Item 237)
      bound volkwein's music paper with bass lines for songs in Act II handwritten in it.
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 4, Folder 237A)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin with handwritten notation "Joe."
    - "Ain't Ya Sorry for What Ya Done" (Box 4, Folder 238-241)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript with handwritten notes. Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed
    - "Ist Act" (Box 4, Folder 238-241, Item 239)
      Handwritten notes. 2 pages. Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed
    - "Franco's Italian Army Marching Song" (Box 4, Folder 238-241, Item 240)
      holograph manuscript. Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed
    - "Songs That Never Made it" (Box 4, Folder 238-241, Item 241)
      Holography manuscript. Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed
    - "Pittsburgh is a Festival City" (Box 4, Folder 242-247, Item 242)
      Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed